graphicsfuel.com 2018-07-30

# Privacy Policy - GraphicsFuel

#### Privacy Policy

Your privacy is very important to us. At GraphicsFuel we have a few fundamental principles that we follow:

We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can’t stand services that ask you for things like your gender or income level for no apparent reason.)

We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.

We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of our site.

#### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, GraphicsFuel collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. GraphicsFuel’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how GraphicsFuel’s visitors use its website. From time to time, GraphicsFuel may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

GraphicsFuel also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on our blogs. GraphicsFuel only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that blog commenter IP addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog where the comment was left.

#### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to GraphicsFuel’s websites choose to interact with GraphicsFuel in ways that require GraphicsFuel to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that GraphicsFuel gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who comment on our blog to provide a username and email address. Those who wish to receive GraphicsFuel updates via email, we collect their emails. In each case, GraphicsFuel collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with GraphicsFuel. GraphicsFuel does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

#### Aggregated Statistics

GraphicsFuel may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, GraphicsFuel may monitor the most popular pages on the GraphicsFuel.com site or use spam screened by the Akismet service to help identify spam. GraphicsFuel may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, GraphicsFuel does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

#### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

GraphicsFuel discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on GraphicsFuel’s behalf or to provide services available at GraphicsFuel’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using GraphicsFuel’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. GraphicsFuel will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, GraphicsFuel discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when GraphicsFuel believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of GraphicsFuel, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an GraphicsFuel website and have supplied your email address, GraphicsFuel may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with GraphicsFuel and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. GraphicsFuel takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

#### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. GraphicsFuel uses cookies to help GraphicsFuel identify and track visitors, their usage of GraphicsFuel website, and their website access preferences. GraphicsFuel visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using GraphicsFuel’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of GraphicsFuel’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

#### Links from this Website

We do not monitor or review the content of other party’s websites which are linked to from this website. Opinions expressed or material appearing on such websites are not necessarily shared or endorsed by us and should not be regarded as the publisher of such opinions or material.

Users may find advertising or other content on GraphicsFuel that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. GraphicsFuel does not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from GraphicsFuel. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to GraphicsFuel, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

#### Service Providers

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services and/or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.

These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform specific tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use your information for any other purpose.

#### Business Transfers

If GraphicsFuel, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that GraphicsFuel goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of GraphicsFuel may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

#### Ads

Ads appearing on GraphicsFuel may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by GraphicsFuel and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

#### Privacy Policy Changes

GraphicsFuel reserves the right to change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in GraphicsFuel’s sole discretion. GraphicsFuel encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
